http://www.isgf.org/index.php/en/organization/privacy-policy

Contact Us
Search ...
English (UK)
Francais (FR)
Text Size
You are here:
Home
Organization
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
INTRODUCTIONISGF is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy and needs to collect and use certain types of information about individuals, members, partners who come into contact with ISGF in order to carry on our work. This personal information must be collected and dealt with appropriately whether it is collected on paper, stored in a computer database, or recorded on other material and there are safeguards to ensure this under the General Data Protection Regulations 2018 (GDPR). This new regulation went into effect in Europe on 25 May 2018.
ISGF will process any personal data disclosed in relation to message boards, surveys and questionnaires, newsletters, appeals, promotions for the purposes of achieving its charitable objectives, fundraising and providing the services it offers in relation to these activities. The data collected by any survey or questionnaire will only be used for the purpose stated on the form. You may also be given the opportunity to add your information to our databases, so we can contact you in the future. We will only use the contact information provided with your permission. In this regard, you are kindly invited to contact the ISGF World Bureau, This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
pdf
Privacy Policy
(90 KB)
FaLang translation system by Faboba
Main Menu
The world and ISGFPublicationsWorld Committee meetings Central Branch (CB)TwinningProjectsInt. Development FundInt. Ambassadors GuildPartnershipsDownloadsPhoto Gallery
Login Form
Username
Password
Remember Me
Forgot your password?
Forgot your username?
